Sherpa says that today, December 10, 2030, the
market is on
its color day, in the same way,
sometimes it
closes with a rise and sometimes it closes with a fall. The
market has its own style, the market has its
own movement,
but
if you have
seen my videos in detail, then
I had said
that the market will boom
in the first and second week
and this market is really booming, this statement of mine is
proved by the fact that
when I say one thing that
I have nothing to do with the rise or fall of the centers,
it is just like a sign, if the
market fell by 2,000 points, then it
felt that the market has fallen a lot, or if it
fell by 400-500 points, then it felt that the market is falling, but
this is all just an indication for me, should
I tell you, today the
Sensex is down by 115 points, right now at the time when I am
recording this video,
but let me tell you that I had
commented on Asian Paints to you at the
price of 2796-286, today it  It has
reached the price of Rs 3276 with a rise of Rs 100.
How many days have passed
and how many days have passed, my brother Asian friends,
today it has reached the price of Rs 3278 with a rise of Rs 100, it must
not have been even a week or ten days, I had
told you about Grasim, today it
is rising at 29-30, Mahindra & Mahindra
is at 935 and most importantly, friend, DSC First
Bank is rising by Rs 2.75,
that the share of Rs 40 has risen by 25 paise in no time,
I had
commented that Siemens is very strong, today with a
rise of around eight percent,
you are seeing it at 2450 with a rise of Rs 178,
I told you how
a dealer developed, there is a rise in the gallon route,
see live, 532 has reached the position of 400 to 500
32, how secretly, how easily, that is
why I say again and again that
when you are in the best space, you are
always in profit.  Will be from the Municipal Commissioner
at a price of Rs 2437 today, rapid progress of 64th
in ₹100 when I commented
2010 sequence definitely commented then this stock is
not looking good for you right diction again
came around ₹500 for me I
repeat this thing again and again so that
somewhere you can also understand that
if a market is down by 24 then
what has happened and what is the big reason
that I should come out of the market,
on the gender stage the share of Genius fell by ₹500 increased to
40 thousand and now I have told you about two-three
videos bank that
it is included in the fifty thousand club, Tej
Industries you should keep in mind this is a
deal of great strength and a very good deal
whether you have been a part of double and
financial is at a good price today you should pay attention to this pay
attention to Manapuram it is at a good price pay
attention to City Union Bank look at Navin Flooring
where it went, whenever there is a correction it
falls twice  When there is a break in the price of any good stock, then
you should not miss that opportunity.
Abhijan Sirmaur's Boss is there for you.
Do not look at the increase of Rs. 100,
my love, Boss is available very quickly. I have
given it a digit of 25 thousand 700. The price today is Rs. 16000, 820.
You
should buy at Shriram Transport, it is a deal of opportunity.
You should buy cement from them,
it is a deal of opportunity. You should buy Deepak Network, it is a
deal of opportunity. So in this
way, how have I been continuously talking about ID?
Many people think that
when will ITC run or not, but
in two days it is up Rs. 12 and today it is 236
friends, a share of ₹10 has come to the price of Rs. 236 today. An
increase of ₹70 and an increase of Rs. 10 is
not a small increase, so be
patient with this plant,
give it some time. A lot is going to happen in it,
like today, Saudi is below the price of Saheb Bhai,
Tata Steel comes in it,
you should pay attention to it.  Gas arrives,
you should pay attention to it, it is ICICI
Lombard, you should pay attention to it and for today's
purchases which I have made on my own, let me
tell you about that,
I have purchased Divi's Labs, again I have
purchased Atul, again I have done
something on SBI card, again now
I have taken a similar big return, again I have
taken IN for A, again and when you
see them, today's price, hence I have taken about
India, again
you will see that price a little bit because today you will see it
in the rate, this is the only opportunity to see some loss
and on this occasion you will have to
understand something for yourself, but how will you listen
friends, see, I have added Coromandel International for three
months
in Mehar Dip, I will keep joining Coromandel International for two to three
months i.e. January-March
and after March when April comes,
then I will think about its structure, whether I have to take five
or ten, Coromandel,
for 1200 rupees grid,
always free or the price of 762 in Coromandel International  It is true that
such things, such opportunities, such money, such
wealth, such benefits, in which market will you get it,
where will you get it, how will you get it by waiting,
I do not understand what to say and
where this purchase can be made, friends, today I have
added more, whereas we have a huge
amount of shares, but six pieces,
I had just saluted the Symbol charging cable,
I have bought it for us and
Nestle is a special buy for me today and I am
giving three medical recommendations for Nestle, you must
buy it for 22500, for 24500, for
25500, for 29500, this target is for
3 to 6 to 9-12 months, I will
definitely make a big buy in this play,
sir, in the end I will say that
you must buy on my 2nd year, Reliance
and the title should be in your photo,
finally I will keep saying that you can
also comment on HDFC HUL shoes, you can buy,
keep buying, there will be a very
good move in ITC, you should watch that too and remember it
You will get very good opportunities in the coming time
and will get huge benefits. Stay tuned, stay
engaged in the stock market and
this is where you will get opportunities. Five of my banks are of yes,
I would like to repeat this again
for you. ICICI Bank, Axis
Bank, Kotak Mahindra Bank, SBI Bank,
buy these banks as well. And
I have said this many times, it is
like my own son. I will buy it
after 20 years of my life. When I am in old age, if there is
such a thing, then it will give me a lot of
strength. I see
IDFC Bank growing tenfold from here in the next ten years.
So you
can become an officer in IDFC First Bank. It is a very
good job, excellent, very good.
You should
include it in your search for a long time. Very
strong, very excellent, very excellent. Come, that's enough
for today. If there are more
things to discuss, we will
meet again after the market. The market is still in its full swing
and there will be some weakness in the coming last two weeks.
But
these three months of January-February-March will be the boom of the Indian
stock market.  It will be of great
speed, you will try to leave
behind the films available at good prices in the previous banner, till
today you will see the registry, especially
I think this is a
very great thing about the Ichchhashakti certificate and this is a great
earning, anyway that's all for today, we will meet again
soon, I will talk again in the next video,
sir like the one in the share market,
sir like the shopkeeper in the share market
today 10 December 2021 Fakir Sabaqat